// An array containing objects, each representing a quiz question and its options
const quizData = [
    {question: "Sun Gate city of the Incas?", // Question text
      a: "Cusco", // Option A text
      b: "Machu Picchu", // Option B text
      c: "Ollantaytambo", // Option C text
      d: "Nazca", // Option D text
      correct: "b", // Correct answer (a, b, c, or d)
    },
    {
      question: "Viking-founded capital of Iceland?",
      a: "Reykjavik",
      b: "Oslo",
      c: "Helsinki",
      d: "Copenhagen",
      correct: "a",
    },
    {
      question: "Which of these is known as the City of Love?",
      a: "Paris",
      b: "Venice",
      c: "Rome",
      d: "Barcelona",
      correct: "a",
    },
    {
      question: "Official language of Brazil?",
      a: "Spanish",
      b: "Portuguese",
      c: "French",
      d: "Italian",
      correct: "b",
    },
    {
      question: "African wildlife safari country?",
      a: "Kenya",
      b: "South Africa",
      c: "Egypt",
      d: "Morocco",
      correct: "a",
    },
    {
      question: "Ancient Greek city?",
      a: "Istanbul",
      b: "Athens",
      c: "Cairo",
      d: "Rome",
      correct: "b",
    },
    {
      question: "Currency of Egypt?",
      a: "Dollar",
      b: "Pound",
      c: "Riyal",
      d: "Dinar",
      correct: "b",
    },
    {
      question: "Historic palace in India?",
      a: "Hawa Mahal",
      b: "Taj Mahal",
      c: "Amber Palace",
      d: "Fatehpur Sikri",
      correct: "b",
    },
    {
      question: "Land of the Pharaohs?",
      a: "Greece",
      b: "Turkey",
      c: "Egypt",
      d: "Italy",
      correct: "c",
    },
    {
      question: "Ancient city destroyed by volcano?",
      a: "Pompeii",
      b: "Herculaneum",
      c: "Rome",
      d: "Athens",
      correct: "a",
    },
    {
      question: "Which country is home to the Big Five safari animals?",
      a: "Brazil",
      b: "Kenya",
      c: "China",
      d: "Russia",
      correct: "b",
    },
    {
      question: "Amazon Rainforest country?",
      a: "Colombia",
      b: "Venezuela",
      c: "Ecuador",
      d: "Brazil",
      correct: "d",
    },
    {
      question: "Which desert is known as the Land of Fire?",
      a: "Sahara",
      b: "Atacama",
      c: "Gobi",
      d: "Kalahari",
      correct: "b",
    },
    {
      question: "Which of these is a US state?",
      a: "California",
      b: "Queensland",
      c: "Lima",
      d: "Quebec",
      correct: "a",
    },
    {
      question: "Capital city of Australia?",
      a: "Sydney",
      b: "Melbourne",
      c: "Canberra",
      d: "Brisbane",
      correct: "c",
    },
  ];